

Career Summary

Experience in designing, developing, implementing and testing computer-based hardware and software. Expert in dealing with components that are found inside computer equipment, as well as the actual devices that contain the computers and the software that runs on those machines.

MOHAMMAD AMIRUL HAQUE

WEB DEVELOPER & UI DESIGNER

Career Objective

I want to put to my creative skills, technologies that I am familiar with, innovative thoughts that will benefit the Organization in the long run and also help me in building my professional career.

Experience

2021 - Present	Deepgreen Studio Sylhet, Bangladesh Managing Director
2020 - 2020	Spider Innovation Sylhet, Bangladesh Senior Web Developer
2019 - 2020	BTS Software Technologies Ltd. Sylhet, Bangladesh Web Developer
2017 - 2019	Soft-All- Software Development Ltd. Sylhet, Bangladesh WordPress Developer & Trainer

Education



Training Summary

2016 - 2016
 WEB DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT
 Sylhet IT Academy, Sylhet, Bangladesh
 Description of the education/course.

Contact

- ★ Sylhet Bangladesh
- **4** +880 1627087441
- **1** +880 1778 539887
- haqueamirul76@gmail.com
- in /mohammad-amirul-haque-7ba46b167/
- f /amirul.haque.90

Skills

Web Design

HTML & CSS Bootstrap React JS



Web Development

WordPress Laravel React JS



UI Design

Photoshop Illustrator



Theme Customization

Divi visual composer



My Portfolio

https://amirulhaque.xyz/

https://github.com/haqueamirul

https://www.behance.net/haqueamiru11d0

https://dribbble.com/haqueamirul76

https://www.codegrape.com/user/CreativePro/portfolio

Few Recent Project

https://thicn.org/ https://woodlandsvenue.com/ https://physiciansac.org/ https://tudorhallvenue.co.uk/ https://rccateringevents.com/

Personal information

Father's Name

Md. Abdul Awal

Mother's Name

Sufia Begum

Date of BirthDate of Birth

10/03/1994

Gender

Male

Marital Status

Unmarried

Nationality

Bangladeshi